dreadcentral.com 2014-02-14

# Privacy Policy - Dread Central

**Dread Central Privacy Policy**

**Overview**

Dread Central Media, LLC’s (“DreadCentral”, "we", "us", "our") is committed to protecting its users’ privacy. This Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”), as set forth below, covers dreadcentral.com (“dreadcentral.com,” the “Site,”) and applies solely to information collected on dreadcentral.com. Please read this Privacy Policy to understand how we will treat personally and non-personally identifiable information we collect on dreadcentral.com. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.

**Information We Collect**  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Site. On some pages, you can make comments, complete user profiles, complete contest entry forms, register to receive newsletters or other digital messaging. The types of personally identifiable information collected at these pages are at least: Name, Address, Email Address.

We do not share any of your personally identifiable information with third parties outside of DreadCentral without your consent You can give this consent by “opting-in” to having your information shared with third parties when the option is available during your online interaction. These third parties may include our marketing partners, who may want specific information to better shape their marketing efforts. Additionally, we may provide the community the opportunity to choose to be sent newsletters and other information. We will not send this information to you unless you “opt in” for these services and publications.

In addition, DreadCentral will not sell, dispose, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent except as specifically set forth in this paragraph and in the preceding paragraph. When you choose to supply DreadCentral with your personally identifiable information, DreadCentral compiles this information in a database with other DreadCentral community members’ information and DreadCentral reserves the right to transfer this information to a successor, related entity or to a third party purchasing or otherwise acquiring DreadCentral’s assets.

If you choose to provide DreadCentral with personally identifiable information, you may remove your information from our databases by sending an email to [info@dreadcentral.com](mailto:info@dreadcentral.com). In this email, you must include your user name and password, and a description of the information you would like to change that cannot be changed by yourself online.

**Third Party Ad Servers**  
DreadCentral uses third party advertising companies and advertising networks to deliver advertisements on the Site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address or email address) about your visits to this or other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, go to <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

DreadCentral is participating in the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (DAA) Self-Regulatory Program for Behavioral Advertising. You can learn more about this program at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>. 

**Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, DreadCentral has put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Children’s Privacy**  
The Site is a general audience website and is intended to be used by adults and teenagers interested in DreadCentral. It is not intended for children, and DreadCentral does not want to collect any personal identifiable information for users who are under the age of 13. The safety of children is very important to DreadCentral and DreadCentral recommends that parents review this Privacy Policy and understand its terms, so that this Site is used only by persons age 13 and over.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
DreadCentral reserves the right, at our discretion, to occasionally update this Privacy Policy to comply with any applicable state or federal regulations, to utilize new technologies or to improve your DreadCentral experience. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. For material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by placing a prominent notice on the Site.

**Disclaimer**  
The information provided in this Privacy Policy should not be construed as giving business, legal, or other advice, or warranting as fail proof, the security of information provided through the Site.

**How To Contact Us**  
Should you have any questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [privacy@dreadcentral.com](mailto:privacy@dreadcentral.com)

Last Updated on May 4, 2012
